What's wrong?
Don't you like it?
Have some soup.
No.
Your bracelet
is pretty.
Ah.
This bracelet
was given to me by my brother-in-law
when he went to France last month.
It's not a big brand,
but I
like it very much.
It's not a big brand,
but the person who designed it
is very special.
Because
she only made two of them.
Do you know this bracelet?
Yan,
Get some tissues.
Honey,
what's wrong?
Why are you so distracted?
I've been
working too much lately.
I'm tired.
It's okay.
In a couple of days,
when Jiang Li joins the company to help you,
you won't be so tired.
By the way, honey,
you know what?
When I tried on the wedding dress the other day,
I was so mad.
They claimed it's a high-end design,
but the dress was so ugly.
Luckily, I met Jiang Li.
She used a white dress with 3D pleats.
Wow,
it looked amazing
just like that.
She's the chief designer
of dark fairy tales
that our mom picked.
With Jiang Li,
I don't have to put up with Jenny
and her weird designs anymore.
By the way, Li,
I was in a hurry to pick up Momo that day,
so I didn't get to talk to you.
Why were you at that wedding dress store?
Because it's run by
is run by my senior.
I wanted to catch up with her,
but I ran into Qianqian instead.
What a coincidence.
Come on,
eat by yourself.
Drink that milk,
okay?
Change the tableware for Miss Jiang Li.
Li,
as you see,
those so-called designers
don't understand me like you do.
I've decided
to let Jiang Li
design my wedding dress.
I believe
Jiang Li will make me
the most radiant bride.
Most designers
would only turn you rich girls
into greenhouse roses.
But Qianqian,
you're different.
You're a phoenix raised in a golden cage.
A wedding dress like a queen's robe
is what suits you.
Your mouth
is sharp,
but I love
what you say.
I'm really
getting to like you more and more.
Come on.
To your marriage into the Lu family,
and to dark fairy tales.
Cheers.
By the way,
Mila gave me a couture dress.
It doesn't fit me.
It must fit you.
Come on.
♪The moon, the moon♪
♪Climbs onto the window♪
♪Raindrops♪
♪Sing softly♪
Darling,
Mr. Liu asked for leave today.
You didn't drink today.
Could you take Jiang Li home?
I'm worried about her being alone.
And you two can talk
about work
on the way.
Okay.
I'll go to the garage to get the car.
OK.
I didn't expect
you to be so talented.
What's the name
of the cello piece
you played today?
It sounds familiar.
No.
It's beautiful.
Thank you.
Slow down on the way back.
Be careful.
Why do you get close to Qianqian?
To get close to you.
Why do you get close to me?
Do you love Lu Qianqian?
Of course, I love her.
You're lying.
You play the role of a good husband,
good father and good son-in-law,
just to cover up the fact that
that you can never cross the gap of your origin,
and the secret in your heart.
Don't say it as if you know me well.
I know you
as well as I know myself.
We all live in disguise,
and do anything for a dark future.
In France,
it was just an accident.
Hello, have you found it?
Boss,
Miss Jiang's information
has been sent to your email.
Do you know where she lives?
She used to live in a hotel.
She checked out a few days ago.
She should have been arranged to another place.
If you find out where he lives,
tell me.
Okay.
Zhou Jian.
Why is he here?
Zhou Jian,
do you love me?
Of course I do.
But
I'm just like a weed now.
What can I give you?
I don't care.
As long as you love me,
I'm the happiest woman in the world.
Mr. Zhou Jian,
will you marry Ms. Su Muchen?
I
will.
Honey,
I've been waiting for you in the bedroom.
I'll come in after finishing my work.
Okay?
Guess
why I was nice to Jiang Li today?
Because of the wedding dress store?
I found out that Jiang Li is a woman with ambition.
As for Lu Xu,
there will be no woman
in this world
who truly loves him.
Moreover,
a woman like Jiang Li
wants to get out of the mud
and climb onto a high branch.
She's very greedy.
As long as
you give her enough benefits,
she will beg you for mercy.
As for Dark Fairy Tale,
such an important project,
getting Jiang Li on board
will be very helpful
to your position in the company.
I know you
as well as I know myself.
We both live in disguise.
fighting for a dark future without scruples.
As an audience,
fireworks are always beautiful.
But if you get too close,
the first thing that chokes your lungs
is the pungent smell of sulfur.
You would say
I'm a bitch
or a scheming woman.
But I'm just
playing with the devil.
Do you know why I chose you?
Because you are a greedy wolf.
You are a socialite who won the French Designer Gold Award
by being Charles's
goddaughter.
Aren't you afraid of inviting wolves into the house?
In the eyes of a hunter,
there is no difference
between a wolf and a dog.
Go seduce Zhou Jian
and make him divorce my sister.
You agreed to my terms.
Shares,
reputation,
resources,
I can give you all of these.
As long as you can meet my requirements,
you can get what you want.
Bring me back to China as your fiancée.